Guide to the Hudson Guild records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series VI: Photographs
  - Water Damaged Prints:
    - Cornell University Class of 1892 Including John Lovejoy Elliott, nd (Box 30, Folder 28034)
    - Miscellaneous, 1920s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 28035-28042)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Scrapbook, 1939-1940 (Box 30, Folder 28043)
  - Small Prints:
    - Art Shows, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 28056)
    - Athletics, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28057)
    - Basketball, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 28058)
    - Beach, ca. 1920 (Box 30, Folder 28059)
    - Book Fairs, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28060)
    - Dan Carpenter, 1950,-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28061)
    - Career Fair, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 28062)
    - Chelsea Park, 1920s (Box 30, Folder 28063)
    - Children, 1910s-1930s (Box 30, Folder 28064)
    - Children, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 28065)
    - Children, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28066)
    - Children, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28067)
    - Children, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28068)
    - Children, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28069)
    - Children, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28070)
    - Christmas, 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28071)
    - Educational Programs, 1990s (Box 30, Folder 28072)
    - John Lovejoy Elliott (Box 30, Folder 28073)
    - Elliott Dinner, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 28074)
    - Group Work Parents Dinner, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28075)
    - Hudson Guild Farm. 1910s-1930s (Box 30, Folder 28076)
    - Hudson Guild Farm, 1910s-1930s (Box 30, Folder 28077)
    - Hudson Guild Farm, 1940s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 28078)
    - Hudson Guild Farm, 1960s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28079)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Anniversary, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28080)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Anniversary, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28081)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Anniversary, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28082)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Buildings, 1920s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28083)
    - Hudson Guild Farm Work Project, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28084)
    - Miscellaneous, 1910s-1920s (Box 30, Folder 28085)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28086)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28087)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 28088)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28089)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28090)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1950s (Box 30, Folder 28091)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 28092)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 28093)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28094)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 30, Folder 28095)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28096)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28097)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28098)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28099)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28100)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 28101)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28101)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28103)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 28104)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 28105)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 28106)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 28107)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 28108)
    - Project Connect, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 28109)
    - Petting Zoo, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 28110)
    - Senior Citizens, 1980s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28111)
    - Servicemen, 1940s (Box 30, Folder 28112)
  - Contact Sheets and Negatives:
    - Study Den, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28113)
    - Teen Sexuality Meeting, 1980s (Box 30, Folder 28114)
    - Contact Sheets, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28115-28142)
    - Contact Sheets, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28143-28169)
    - Contact Sheets, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28170-28196)
    - Contact Sheets, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28197-28223)
    - Centennial Exhibit Copy Negatives, 1910s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28224-28243)
    - Dentist, ca. 1930 (Box 30, Folder 28244)
    - Hudson Guild Farm, ca. 1940 (Box 30, Folder 28225-28258)
    - Hudson Guild Farm, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28259-28260)
    - Miscellaneous, 1910s-1960s (Box 30, Folder 28261)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28262)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1990s (Box 30, Folder 28263)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990s (Box 30, Folder 28264-28269)
  - Slides:
    - Art Gallery, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 28270)
    - Camp Madison-Felicia, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 28271)
    - Co-op, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 28272)
    - Hudson Guild Farm, 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 28273-28277)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 28278)
    - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 28279-28281)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 28282-28284)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28285-28294)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28295-28305)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28306-28309)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s-1980s (Box 30, Folder 28310-28311)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 28312-28313)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 28314-28316)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 28317-28318)
    - Miscellaneous, ca. 1990 (Box 30, Folder 28319-28327)
    - Performances, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 28328-28329)
- Series VII: Film and Videotape
  - Camp Madison-Felicia, Summer 1990 JVC VHS-C XR video tape (Box 31)
  - Camp Madison-Felicia, Summer 1990 Softball Game vs. Camp Clearpool, JVC VHS-C XR video tape (Box 31)
  - Camp Madison-Felicia, Summer 1990 Talent Show, JVC VHS-C XR video tape (Box 31)
  - Hudson Guild Pre-Camp Madison Felicia, June 1990 JVC VHS-C TC-20 ER video tape (Box 31)
  - Hudson Guild Karate/Judo, nd, TDK VHS-C E-HG TC-20 video tape (Box 31)
  - "Your Brother's House," nd,16mm black and white composite print (Box 31)
- Name and Subject Index
  - Adler, Felix: Series 2, Folder 30-32
  - Carnegie Corporation, Series 4.1, Folder 2
  - Coit, Stanton: Series 2, Folder 31
  - Columbia University: Series 3.1, Folder 77
  - Educational Alliance: Series 1.1, Folder 27
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies: Series 1.1, Folder 27
  - Ford Foundation: Series 4.1, Folder 5-6
  - Harvard University: Series 4.1, Folder 2, 5
  - Henry Street Settlement: Series 4.1, Folder 21
  - Lee, R. Edward: Series 1.1, Folder 6; Series 3.1, Folder 72
  - Lehman, Herbert H.: Series 3.1, Folder 73
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood House: Series 1.2, Folder 40
  - National Federation of Settlements: Series 1.1, Folder 26; Series 2, Folder 46-47
  - New School for Social Research: Series 1.1, Folder 21
  - New York City Board of Education: Series 4.1, Folder 2, 5-6
  - New York City Housing Authority: Series 2, Folder 50; Series 3.1, Folder 15-16, 18
  - New York University: Series 2, Folder 62; Series 3.1, Folder 77; Series 3.3, Folder 14; Series 4.1, Folder 15
  - Public Education Association: Series 3.2, Folder 4-5
  - Reynolds, James Bronson: Series 2, Folder 55
  - Sutton, Percy: Series 2, Folder 4
  - Union Settlement Association: Series 2, Folder 54
  - United Neighborhood Houses: Series 1.1, Folder 26
  - University Settlement: Series 2, Folder 55